expandrive.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | ExpanDrive

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how ExpanDrive, Inc. and its affiliates (“ExpanDrive,” “we,” “our” or “us”) collect, use, and share information in connection with your use of our websites (including www.expandrive.com), services, and applications (collectively, the “Services”). This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) does not apply to information our customers may process when using our Services.

We may collect and receive information about users of our Services (“users,” “you,” or “your”) from various sources, including: (i) information you provide through your license on the Services (your “Account”) if you register for the Services; (ii) your use of the Services; and (iii) from third-party websites, services, and partners.

We recommend that you read this Privacy Policy in full to ensure you are fully informed. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or ExpanDrive data collection, use, and disclosure practices, please contact us at [support@expandrive.com](mailto:support@expandrive.com).

### Information You Provide

  1. **Registration.**  When you activate ExpanDrive, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name and email address. We also collect information about ExpanDrive license activations for the purposes of advertising promotions and licensing enforcement.
  2. **Payment Information.**  When you purchase a license or subscription in our online store your financial account information is directed to our third-party payment processor. We do not store your financial account information on our systems
  3. **Communications.**  If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide. We may also receive a confirmation when you open an email from us.

### Information We Collect When You Use Our Services.

  1. **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.**  As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. In addition, when you use our Services, we may collect certain information automatically from your device.  This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, landing page, and referring URL. To collect this information, a cookie may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Services. Cookies contain a small amount of information that allows our web servers to recognize you. We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or clear gifs to record your preferences.

**  
** We do not collect the usernames, passwords, server names and drive-configuration settings  in our software nor  is any of this info transmitted to ExpanDrive, Inc.

**What Do we do with the Information we collect?**  
We will use contact information to email purchase receipts, software update notifications, security update notifications as well as a few helpful emails to get started with the software. We also may occasionally send out a promotional email. Nothing more than once per month and all promotional emails will have a link allowing to opt-out of all future emails.

**Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information  
**Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect personal information from you only (i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you; (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights; or (iii) where we have your consent to do so.  We have a legitimate interest in developing our Services and communicating with you as necessary to provide this, for example when responding to your queries, improving our software or undertaking marketing.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information).

**Your Choices  
**You can use some of the features of the Services without registering, thereby limiting the type of information that we collect.

You may unsubscribe from receiving certain promotional emails from us. If you wish to do so, simply follow the instructions found at the end of the email. Even if you unsubscribe, we may still contact you for informational, transactional, account-related, or similar purposes.

Many browsers have an option for disabling cookies, which may prevent your browser from accepting new cookies or enable selective use of cookies. Please note that, if you choose not to accept cookies, some features and the personalization of our Services may no longer work for you. You will continue to receive advertising material but it will not be tailored to your interests.

**Disclosure**  
We won’t disclose your email address, or other personal information, to anyone unless we reasonably believe it is necessary to comply with a subpoena, court order, law, or regulation we may disclose your personal information or file data to the extent required to fulfill our legal obligation.

**Security  
**All personal information is collected via https secure communication and is kept in a secure database that is not subject to any unauthorized usage. We employ a variety of security technologies and measures designed to protect information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information. However, please bear in mind that the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**Data Retention**  
We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax, or accounting requirements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**Access**  
You may request access to information associated with your account by emailing support@expandrive.com.

**Business transfer**  
If ExpanDrive is involved in a business acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, or bankruptcy then your personal information may be transferred as part of the restructuring. We promise that either the acquiring institution will respect your personal information and file data in accordance with this privacy policy, or that you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of the transfer.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, so please review it frequently. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our websites. If we materially change the ways in which we use or share personal information previously collected from you through our Services, we will notify you through our Services, by email, or other communication.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at [support@expandrive.com](mailto:support@expandrive.com).
